(Penny:)It's getting creepy again.
(Raj:)What?
(Penny:)Just thinking about the day
(Penny:)I met you and Leonard.
(Sheldon:)It was a Monday afternoon.
(Sheldon:)You joined us for Indian food.
(Penny:)Can you believe
it's been eight years?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and you're
still eating our food.
(Penny:)I... can't remember a time
(Penny:)you guys weren't in my life.
(Sheldon:)I remember it perfectly.
(Sheldon:)But I have an eidetic memory.
(Sheldon:)If you're interested,
I also remember
(Sheldon:)how much you owe us
for the food.
(alarm beeping)
(Sheldon:)That's it.
(Penny:)That wasn't so bad.
(Sheldon:)No, it wasn't.
(Sheldon:)Uh, now let's tabulate
(Sheldon:)the results of the experiment.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)I think it's safe to say that
you're not in love with me